我们要求15位恐同人士去拥抱陌生同性恋人士
You like women? Yes
你喜欢女人？是的
How's it going? -  Good.
你过得怎么样？ 好的
I'm Adam.  - I'm Jeff, nice to meet you
我是亚当 -我是杰夫，很高兴认识你
Hi I'm Kaitlyn
你好，我是凯特琳
You look nervous
你看起来非常焦虑
I'm always nervous
我总是很焦虑
Why?
为什么呢？
I'm a pretty nervous guy
我是一个非常容易焦虑的人
This is Keddy
我是凯迪
Hi nice to meet you
嗨，很高兴认识你
Why did you ever think it was a sin?
为什么你一直认为这是罪恶的
Because it says so in the Bible
因为圣经里是这么说的
So which one of you is gay?
所以这里谁是同性恋啊？
Right here
这里
We were taught that it's wrong
我们一直被告知这就是错的
How do you kiss another guy? I don't get that
你怎么去亲另一个男生？我没法想象这个
The same way you kiss another girl
就和你如何去亲另一个女生是一样的
So are you gay?
所以你是同性恋？
Yeah
是的
You're so pretty to be gay
你是一个很漂亮的同性恋
I feel like gay men have more sex than straight men
我感觉男同性恋比直男有更多的性生活
I don't know I've been with my boyfriend for 10 years
我不知道，我和我男友已经在一起10年了
and I've never had sex with anybody else
并且我从来没有和别人有过性生活
Well I play the banjo
嗯…我会弹班卓琴
That's cute
很可爱
I don't have a natural response to that
我没办法自如地去回答你
You're kind of cute
你真可爱
That doesn't hurt. It doesn't hurt? No
这也没那么难受。这会使你不快吗？不会
I like your lipstick
我喜欢你的口红
Thank you
谢谢你
I could do without the gay parade
我可以很自如地，如果没有同性恋环绕我身边的话
Then don't go
你不在那个环境里啊
If you didn't know would you think I was gay?
如果你不知道你会认为我是一个同性恋者吗？
Yeah
会
You'd knew?
你会知道吗？
Yeah
会啊
Really?
真的吗？
Of course I mean look at you you're gorgeous
当然，我的意思是你看起来很美丽
We can start with a handshake
我们可以先从握手开始
Hello
你好
Do you want to just go for it?
你想只是来个拥抱吗？
I've never you know
我从来没有抱过，你知道的
Should we start with hugging first
我们能先从拥抱开始吗
Fine fine
当然可以
Okay now give a good. Oh yeah there we go
哦现在放轻松，我们已经开始拥抱了
It's okay right?
这还好对吗？
You're easy to hug
你很轻松地拥抱了
Squishing, our boobs together. Okay.
靠近点，让我们的胸贴胸，好的
Okay lets bring it in for a hug here
来吧让我们在这拥抱
I'll try not to hug too strong
我会尝试不那么僵硬地抱你
It's going to be a bro hug?
这是一个朋友之间的拥抱是吗
I did shave before coming, so I'm probably a little less scary
我来之前确实刮过胡子，所以我可能没那么害怕
Where?
哪里
My face
我的脸
Okay
好的
You kind of remind me of my husband do you know that?
你知道吗你有点像，你让我想起了我的丈夫
I'm still normal you're still normal
我很正常，你也很正常
Same people just hugging
只是相同的人拥抱
You rock it like a super star
你像超级明星一样摇滚
Yeah absolutely
是的，当然
You seem like a cool guy
你看起来很酷
I just think your whole sex thing is kind of gross
我只是认为你的性生活有些恶心
I think your whole sex thing is kind of gross
我认为你的性生活也有些恶心
Fair enough
足够公平
It's true
是的